questionsTwo = [
       {
        "Question":"1. Which of these collections defines a LIST?",
        "choices": [
                "('apple', 'banana', 'cherry')",
                "['apple', 'banana', 'cherry']",
                "{'name':'apple', 'color': 'green'}",
                "{'apple', 'banana', 'cherry'}",
        ],
        "Answer": "['apple', 'banana', 'cherry']",
    },
    {
        "Question":"2. Which of these collections defines a TUPLE?",
        "choices": [
                "('apple', 'banana', 'cherry')",
                "['apple', 'banana', 'cherry']",
                "{'apple', 'banana', 'cherry'}",
                "{'name':'apple', 'color': 'green'}",
        ],
        "Answer": "('apple', 'banana', 'cherry')",
    },
    {
        "Question":"3. Which of these collections defines a SET?",
        "choices": [
                "('apple', 'banana', 'cherry')",
                "['apple', 'banana', 'cherry']",
                "{'name':'apple', 'color': 'green'}",
                "{'apple', 'banana', 'cherry'}",
        ],
        "Answer": "{'apple', 'banana', 'cherry'}",
    },
    {
        "Question":"4. Which of these collections defines a DICTIONARY?",
        "choices": [
                "('apple', 'banana', 'cherry')",
                "['apple', 'banana', 'cherry']",
                "{'name':'apple', 'color': 'green'}",
                "{'apple', 'banana', 'cherry'}",
        ],
        "Answer": "{'name':'apple', 'color': 'green'}",
    },
    {
        "Question":"5. Which collection is ordered, changeable, and allows duplicate members?",
        "choices": [
                "TUPLE",
                "DICTIONARY",
                "SET",
                "LIST",
        ],
        "Answer": "LIST",
    },
    {
        "Question":"6. Which collection does not allow duplicate members?",
        "choices": [
                "TUPLE",
                "SET",
                "LIST",
                "DICTIONARY",
        ],
        "Answer": "SET",
    },
    {
        "Question":"7. How do you start writing a if statement in Python?",
        "choices": [
                "if x > y:",
                "if x > y then:",
                "if (x > y)",
                "if x > y done",
        ],
        "Answer": "if x > y:",
    },
    {
        "Question":"8. How do you start writing a while loop in Python?",
        "choices": [
                "x > y while {",
                "while x > y:",
                "while x > y {",
                "while (x > y)",
        ],
        "Answer": "while x > y:",
    },
    {
        "Question":"9. How do you start writing a for loop in Python?",
        "choices": [
                "for x > y:",
                "for each x in y:",
                "for x in y:",
                "for (x > y):",
        ],
        "Answer": "for x in y:",
    },
    {
        "Question":"10. Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
        "choices": [
                "exit",
                "break",
                "stop",
                "return",
        ],
        "Answer": "break",
    },
]


